token	NER
The	O
Computational	I-ORG
Lexicology	I-ORG
and	O
Terminology	I-ORG
Lab	I-ORG
headed	O
by	O
Piek	I-PER
Vossen	I-PER
offers	O
mutliple	O
courses	O
in	O
English	O
.	O
